Guide to the Chet Huntley Papers 1912-2017
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Awards, Memorials, and Memorabilia, 1954-1974; Series XI; 6.0 linear feet
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Outstanding Program Achievement in the Field of News, 1961-1962; 78(XI):20 (Box 25)
  - Order of the Grizzly Award, University of Montana, 1966 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Adelphi University, Achievement Award, undated (Box-folder 20/2)
  - American Hungarian Studies Foundation, George Washington Award, 1970 (Box-folder 20/3)
    Corresponds with 78(XI):13
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Outstanding Achievement in Coverage of Special Events (nomination), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Outstanding Achievement within Regularly Scheduled News Programs (nomination), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Outstanding Achievement in News Documentary Programming (nomination), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Boston University - Honorary Doctorate of Letters (Literature), 1962 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Franklin & Marshall - Honorary Doctorate of Literature, 1964 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - California Association of Secondary School Administrators - Certificate of contributing membership, undated (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Los Angeles Alumnae of Theta Sigma Phi - Certificate of Special Recognition, 1954 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - George Foster Peabody Radio Award, 1954 (Box-folder 23OS/3)
    Corresponds with 78(XI):14
  - Alfred I. Dupont Awards Foundation, Commentator Award, 1956 (Box-folder 23OS/4)
  - Memorial to Chet Huntley from Directors of Big Sky, 1974 (Box-folder 23OS/5)
  - Robert E. Sherwood Award, 1958 (Box-folder 23OS/6)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, Certificate of Appreciation, undated (Box-folder 23OS/7)
  - International University of Communications, Master of Arts, 1974 (Box-folder 23OS/8)
  - George Foster Peabody Broadcasting Award, 1969 (Box-folder 23OS/9)
  - International Radio and Television Society Inc., Broadcaster of the Year Award, 1970 (Box-folder 23OS/10)
    Corresponds with 78(XI):3
  - Credit Union National Association Memorial/Resolution, 1974 (Box-folder 23OS/11)
  - Woodrow Wilson Memorial Commission, 1962 (Box-folder 23OS/1)
  - Broadcast Advertising Club of Chicago Award of Merit, 1968; 78(XI):1 (Box 25)
  - Academy of Television Arts and Sciences at New York, Outstanding Contribution to Television News and Public Affairs, 1961; 78(XI):2 (Box 26OS)
  - International Radio and Television Society Inc. Broadcaster of the Year Award, 1970; 78(XI):3 (Box 26OS)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, Distinguished Service Award, 1967; 78(XI):4 (Box 26OS)
  - University of Southern California School of Journalism and Alumni Association Distinguished Achievement Award of the Year, 1960; 78(XI):5 (Box 25)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Outstanding Program Achievement in the Field of News, 1959-1960; 78(XI):6 (Box 25)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, Best Radio or TV Interpretation of Foreign Affairs, 1957; 78(XI):7 (Box 25)
  - Boston University, Sigma Delta Chi, "Outstanding Broadcast Journalism" award, 1965; 78(XI):8 (Box 25)
  - Finlandia Foundation, N.Y. Metropolitan Chapter, Inc., Arts and Letters Award, 1962; 78(XI):9 (Box 25)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 25th Anniversary Award, 1972; 78(XI):10 (Box 25)
  - Institute of Human Relations, Mass Media Award, 1970; 78(XI):11 (Box 25)
  - TV Guide Plaque, undated; 78(XI):12 (Box 25)
- Artwork, ca 1950s and 1972; Series XII; 3 items
  This series includes two bronze sculptures of Chet Huntley. The Chrysler Realty Corporation commissioned these sculptures in preparation for the opening of the Big Sky Resort. Derek Wernher completed the sculptures in 1972. In 2018 a sketch by American illustrator Leo Hershfield was moved from the 'biographical' folder in Series I to this series.
  - Bronze sculpture, Chet Huntley in sheep skin coat, 1972; 78(XII):1
  - Bronze sculpture, Chet Huntley leaning on a fence rail, 1972; 78(XII):2
  - Portrait of a Senator [Mike Mansfield] by Leo Hershfield, circa 1960s; Inscribed: For Tippy who asked for drawing of her favorite Senator who happens to be one of mine, too. (Box-folder 1/19)
- Accession 2019-003, Series XIII; 2.5 linear feet
  The materials in this series were donated to Archives and Special Collections in 2018 by Sharon Huntley Kahn, Chet Huntley's daughter, and include materials compiled by Kahn and materials given to Kahn by Tippy Huntley.
  Materials in this series were organized by broad topic. Folders for each topic were then arranged chronologically. Audio recordings donated with this accession were placed into Series X.
  - Personal: Scrapbook Pages (probably compiled by his mother), 1929-1960 (Box-folder OS 29/2)
  - Personal: Autograph Book (Going Away Gift) From Work Colleagues, circa 1936 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - Personal: Chet Huntley, Tipton Stringer Marriage Announcement and Clippings, 1959 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Personal: Promotional Materials for Chet Huntley, undated (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Personal: Memorial Reception and Tributes, 1974 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Writings by Huntley: "A Word for the War", December 6, 1942 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Writings by Huntley: Miscellaneous, 1967-1974 and undated (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Writings by Huntley: Col. Business Columns, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Writings by Huntley: "Journalism" Speech, undated (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Writings by Huntley: Incomplete (pages missing), undated (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Books: News Analysis - What's Really Happening in the World Today, 1966 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Books: The Generous Years, Fawcett Crest paperback, 1970 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Books: The Generous Years, in Thai language, 1972 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Clippings and Writings: Clippings, 1959-1974 (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Clippings and Writings: About New Jersey Farm, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Clippings and Writings: Kron-TV Election Guide (San Francisco Chronicle), July 16, 1964 (Box-folder OS 29/1)
  - Clippings and Writings: About Chet Huntley's Childhood, 1968-1986 and undated (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Clippings and Writings: About Retiring From NBC, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Clippings and Writings: "The Chet Huntleys" by Jack Beall, undated (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Clippings and Writings: About Huntley's Death, 1974 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Tippy Huntley: Writings by Tippy Huntley, 1961-1977 and undated (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Tippy Huntley: Clippings About Tippy Huntley, 1961-1999 (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Big Sky Resort: Clippings About Huntley and Big Sky, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Big Sky Resort: Clippings and Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 and undated (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Big Sky Resort: Promotional Photographs (including of Huntleys), circa 1970s (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Big Sky Resort: Photo of Interior of Huntley House at Big Sky, circa 1970s (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Big Sky Resort: Promotional Materials, circa 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Big Sky Resort: Master Plan Map, undated (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Photographs: Huntley as Baby, circa 1912 (Box-folder 28/9)
  - Photographs: Chet, Wadine and Marian Huntley, circa 1917 (Box-folder 28/10)
  - Photographs: Huntley as Young Man, circa 1930s (Box-folder 28/11)
  - Photographs: Huntley as Young Man (portrait), circa 1930s (Box-folder 28/12)
  - Photographs: Huntley Posing with KERN Microphone, signed photograph, circa 1940s (Box-folder 28/13)
  - Photographs: Huntley Posing with CBS Microphone, circa 1940s (Box-folder 28/14)
  - Photographs: Huntley Walking, with ABC Logo Behind Him, circa 1951-1955 (Box-folder 28/15)
  - Photographs: Huntley at Speaking Engagement, 1953 (Box-folder 28/16)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley with Daryl Zanuck. With Randolph Scott and Walter Brennan. With Governor Chandler of Kentucky. All in front of KECA microphone., ca 1950s (Box-folder 28/17)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley and David Brinkley, Election Night, 1964 (Box-folder 28/18)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley in Moscow, 1965 (Box-folder 28/19)
  - Photographs: Huntley Posing Near Airplane [photo by Jim Davidson], 1967 (Box-folder 28/20)
  - Photographs: Huntley with His Daughter, Sharon, Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box-folder 28/21)
  - Photographs: Various NBC Photos, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/22)
  - Photographs: Huntley with Dog, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/23)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley and Tippy Huntley, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/24)
  - Photographs: Signed Portrait of Chet Huntley, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/25)
  - Photographs: Huntley Smoking Pipe, Typing. Rolltop Desk in Background, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/26)
  - Photographs: From New Jersey Farm, circa 1960s (Box-folder 28/27)
  - Photographs: Huntley in Vietnam Interviewing General Westmoreland, circa 1965 (Box-folder 28/28)
  - Photographs: Huntley Outdoors, Including Fishing and Horseback Riding, circa 1960s-1970s (Box-folder 28/29)
  - Photographs: "Chet's Report on Migrant Workers", circa 1970 (Box-folder 28/30)
  - Photographs: Tipton "Tippy" Huntley, circa 1970 (Box-folder 28/31)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley and Tippy Huntley, circa 1970-1974 (Box-folder 28/32)
  - Photographs: Huntley on His NBC Retirement Gift, a Tennessee Walker (horse), circa 1971 (Box-folder 28/33)
  - Photographs: Tipton Stringer Huntley, undated (Box-folder 28/34)
  - Photographs: Chet Huntley and Reuven Frank, undated (Box-folder 28/35)
  - Retrospectives: Television Academy Hall of Fame Program, 1988 (Box-folder 28/36)
  - Retrospectives: Celebration in Honor of the 50th Anniversary of the Huntley-Brinkley Report and Remembering Reuven Frank, Program and DVD, 2006 (Box-folder 28/37)
  - Retrospectives: Homesteads to Huntley, Documentary About Huntley and Big Sky Resort, by Sharon Huntley Kahn, 2017 (Box-folder 28/38)